Contact

abdelrahmanrezk1997@gmail.c

www.linkedin.com/in/abdelrahman-rezk-3b1333216 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Development Tools
Team Development
Machine Learning

Certifications

Udacity Machine Learning Engineer Nanodegree

Structuring Machine Learning Projects

Machine Learning Stanford University

Discrete Math and Analyzing Social Graphs

Achieving 3d place in Deep Learning competition

Abdelrahman Rezk

Machine Learning Researcher and Developer at OrderGO Cairo

Summary

Innovative, self learner developer and researcher interested in the fascinating world of data in it's several shapes specifically the images data, my specialty is to learn and implement machine learning algorithms and integrate it in a real world solutions that serve the humanity by saving humans time and effort.

Experience

OrderGO

Machine Learning Researcher and Developer August 2021 - Present (5 months)

InnoVision Industries
Computer Vision Engineer
September 2019 - May 2020 (9 months)

Education

Ain Shams University

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (September 2015 - June 2019)